Cioni, Peter J. Labor Agreement Collection 5916
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Peter J. Cioni Labor Agreement Collection
1925-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Cioni, Peter J.
5916
4.11 cubic feet
4.1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5734522
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 18, 2000
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6034: Rare Pamphlet Collection
Arrangement
Series I. COMPANY PUBLICATIONS & DOCUMENTS
Sub-Series A. AGREEMENTS Sub-Series B. PUBLICATIONS
Series II. GENERAL POLITICS
Sub-Series A. General - Political Sub-Series B. Civil Rights Sub-Series C. Nixon-McGovern Presidential Election Sub-Series D. Viet Nam War
Series III. MONOGRAPHS
Series IV. NATIONAL RIGHT TO WORK COMMITTEE
Series V. SCHOLARLY PUBLICATION
Series VI. UNION (ANTI) PROPAGANDA
Series VII. UNION MEMORABILIA
Series VIII. UNION PAMPHLETS
Sub-Series A. BYLAWS Sub-Series B. UNION PAMPHLETS, BROCHURES, MISCELLANEOUS PUBLICATIONS
Series IX. MISCELLANEOUS PHOTOGRAPHS
Cioni, Peter J.; Daffara, John.; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers.; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; Comunication Workers of America; Distillery, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; International Die Sinkers' Conference; International Molders and Allied Workers Union; International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine & Furniture Workers-Communications Workers of America; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association.; Textile Workers Union of America; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America.; United Furniture Workers of America.; United Mine Workers of America; United Plant Guard Workers of America.; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America; United Steelworkers of America; Utility Workers Union of America
5734522
- Series I. COMPANY PUBLICATIONS & DOCUMENTS
  - Sub-Series A. AGREEMENTS
    - Acme Industries, Inc., 1949-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Item 1: Acme Industries, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, affiliated with American Federation of Labor (UAW), Local 755, 1949- 1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Scope and Contents
        7/22/49 - 7/22/50.
      - Item 2: Acme Industries, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, affiliated with American Federation of Labor (UAW), Local 755, 1955- 1958; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 1)
        8/24/55 - 8/24/58.
    - Adco Products, Inc. and Its Employees, 1976-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 2)
      4/5/76 - 12/5/77
    - Aeroquip Corporation, Aeroquip Aerospace Division of Jackson, Michigan and UAW, Local 475, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      11/2/77 - 9/15/80.
    - Alabama By-Products Corporation and United Steel Workers of America (USA), District 36, 1983-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 4)
      12/17/83 - 6/30/87
    - Albion Malleable Iron Company and International Molders' and Foundry Workers' Union of North America (IMAW), Local 413, 1947-1948; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 5)
      1/17/47 - 1/17/48
    - American Distilling Co., Inc. and Distillery, Wine & Allied Workers' International Union, Local 4, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 6)
      1/15/71 - 1/15/74
    - American Lava Corporation and UAW, Local 222, 1953; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 7)
      9/28/1953
    - AMI Incorporated and United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UE), Local 918, 1954-1956; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 8)
      11/8/54 - 10/15/56
    - B.F. Goodrich Company, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Item 1: B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO-CLC (URW), Local 715, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 9)
        5/31/73 - 4/20/76.
      - Item 2: B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO-CLC (URW), Local 715, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 9)
        5/31/73 - 4/20/76. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO-CLC (URW), Local 5, 715, 43, 241, 318, 281, 351, 1973- 1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 9)
        5/31/73 - 4/20/76. Agreement on Employee Benefit Programs.
      - Item 4: B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO-CLC (URW), Local 5, 715, 43, 241, 318, 281, 351, 1973- 1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 9)
        5/31/73 - 4/20/76. Amended Agreement on Supplemental Unemployment Benefits.
    - Bowmar Instrument Corporation, Fort Wayne, Indiana and UAW, Local 1389, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 10)
      11/22/75 - 11/21/78.
    - Buick Motor Division of General Motor Corporation, Flint Michigan and UAW-CIO, Local 599, 1947; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 11)
      3/13/1947
    - Canadian Clark, Ltd., of St. Thomas, Ontario and International Association of Machinists & Aerospace Workers (IAM), Local 2183, 1956-1957; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 12)
      11/19/56 - 11/19/57.
    - Chambers, Bering, Quinlan Co. and International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America, AFL-CIO, (AIW) Local 741, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 13)
      6/2/75 - 6/2/78
    - Chrysler Corporation and UAW, Local 3, 7, 47, 51, 140, 227, 230, 371, 375, 490, 685, 705, 1946-1947; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 14)
      1/26/46 - 1/26/47
    - Clark Equipment Company, Axle Division and United Plant Guard Workers of America (PGW), Local 7, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 15)
      1/24/73 - 3/25/76.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America (IBT), Local 34, 1956-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America (IBT), Local 34, 1956-1958; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 16)
        2/1/56 - 1/31/56. Agreement and Wage Scale.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America (IBT), Local 34, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 16)
        2/1/61 - 1/31/64. Agreement.
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America (IBT), Local 34, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 16)
        9/1/73 - 9/1/76. Agreement.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Detroit Plant, Delfield Division and Sheet Metal Workers' International Association (SMW), Local 80, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 17)
      10/1/73 - 9/30/76
    - Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, Nashville Sales & Service Branch, Nashville, Tennessee and IAM, District Lodge 155, 1973- 1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 18)
      5/1/73 - 4/30/76
    - Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, Denver Sales & Service Branch, Denver, Colorado and UAW, Local 186, 1962-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 19)
      4/1/62 - 3/31/64. ... 4/1/73 - 3/31/76
    - Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division, Detroit Sales & Service Branch and UAW, Local 212, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 20)
      10/1/62 - 10/1/64
    - Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1958-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1958-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        11/1/58 - 12/1/61.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1958-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        11/1/58 - 12/1/61. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        2/26/62 - 5/1/65.
      - Item 4: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        2/26/62 - 5/1/65. Copy 2.
      - Item 5: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/31/65 - 5/1/68.
      - Item 6: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/68 - 5/1/71.
      - Item 7: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/71 - 5/1/74.
      - Item 8: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/71 - 5/1/74. Copy 2.
      - Item 9: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/74 - 5/1/77.
      - Item 10: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/74 - 5/1/77. Copy 2.
      - Item 11: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/77 - 5/1/80.
      - Item 12: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/77 - 5/1/80. Copy 2.
      - Item 13: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/80 - 5/1/83.
      - Item 14: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/80 - 5/1/83. Copy 2.
      - Item 15: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        2/26/62 - 5/1/65. Supplemental Agreement: Pension Plan.
      - Item 16: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        2/26/62 - 5/1/65. Supplemental Agreement: Pension Plan. Copy 2.
      - Item 17: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/71 - 5/1/74. Supplemental Agreement: Pension Plan.
      - Item 18: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/71 - 5/1/74. Supplemental Agreement: Pension Plan. Copy 2.
      - Item 19: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Item 20: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Item 21: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 281 (Clerical Unit), 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        5/1/80 - 5/1/83. Supplemental Agreement: Pension Plan.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Industrial Truck Division Flint Depot of Detroit Sales and Service Branch and IBT, Local 332, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 22)
      3/26/62 - 3/23/65
    - Clark Equipment Company, Press and Metal Fabrication Division and United Furniture Workers of America (UFWA), Local 415, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 23)
      2/1/74 - 1/31/77
    - Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, Reading, Pennsylvania and IBT, Local 429, 1994-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 24)
      10/1/94 - 9/30/64.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Linden, New Jersey and IAM, Lodge 447, District 15, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 25)
      9/28/73 - 9/27/76
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, Linden Sales & Service Branch, Linden, New Jersey and IAM, Lodge 447, District 15, 1973- 1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 25)
        9/28/73 - 9/27/76.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Buchanan, Michigan and UAW, Local 468, 1955-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 26)
      11/28/55 -11/25/58. ...5/16/74 - 5/15/77.
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Buchanan, Michigan and UAW, Local 468, 1955-1958; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 26)
        11/28/55 -11/25/58.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Buchanan, Michigan and UAW, Local 468, 1955-1958; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 26)
        11/28/55 -11/25/58. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Buchanan, Michigan and UAW, Local 468, 1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 26)
        4/16/62. Supplemental Agreements: Unemployment Benefit Plan and Pension Plan.
      - Item 4: Clark Equipment Company, Buchanan, Michigan and UAW, Local 468, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 26)
        5/16/74 - 5/15/77.
      - Item 5: Clark Equipment Company, Buchanan, Michigan and UAW, Local 468, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 26)
        5/16/74 - 5/15/77. Copy 2.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Tyler Refrigeration Division, Waxahachie, Texas and UAW, Local 514, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 27)
      6/1/73 - 5/31/76
    - Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Gwinner, North Dakota and AIW, Local 560, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 28)
      12/1/73 - 12/3/76
    - Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Cooperstown, North Dakota and AIW, Local 563, 1970-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Cooperstown, North Dakota and AIW, Local 563, 1970-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 29)
        12/21/70 - 12/14/73.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Cooperstown, North Dakota and AIW, Local 563, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 29)
        12/15/73 - 12/17/76.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Bismarck, North Dakota and AIW, Local 566, 1973-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Bismarck, North Dakota and AIW, Local 566, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 30)
        11/19/73 - 11/19/76.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Bismarck, North Dakota and AIW, Local 566, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 30)
        11/20/76 - 11/16/79.
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Bismarck, North Dakota and AIW, Local 566, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 30)
        11/20/76 - 11/16/79. Copy 2.
      - Item 4: Clark Equipment Company, Melrose Division, Bismarck, North Dakota and AIW, Local 566, 1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 30)
        1/1/74. Supplemental Agreement: Pension Plan.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Mt. Pleasant Plant, Delfield Division and AIW, Local 585, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 31)
      6/1/74 - 5/31/77.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Gear & Forge Division, Jackson County, Michigan and UAW, Local 623, 1949-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Gear & Forge Division, Jackson County, Michigan and UAW, Local 623, 1949-1952; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        6/15/49 - 3/1/52.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Gear & Forge Division, Jackson County, Michigan and UAW, Local 623, 1949-1952; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        6/15/49 - 3/1/52. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Gear & Forge Division, Jackson County, Michigan and UAW, Local 623, 1950-1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        8/9/50 - 12/31/55.
      - Item 4: Clark Equipment Company, Gear & Forge Division, Jackson County, Michigan and UAW, Local 623, 1950-1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        8/9/50 - 12/31/55. Copy 2.
      - Item 5: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Item 6: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan and Pension Plan, 1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        2/26/62.
      - Item 7: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan and Pension Plan, 1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        2/26/62. Copy 2.
      - Item 8: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Item 9: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan and Pension Plan, 1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/31/1965.
      - Item 10: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan and Pension Plan, 1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/31/1965. Copy 2.
      - Item 11: Clark Equipment Company, Apprentice Standards., 1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        7/20/65.
      - Item 12: Clark Equipment Company, Apprentice Standards., 1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        7/20/65. Copy 2.
      - Item 13: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        1/1/68 - 5/1/71.
      - Item 14: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Agreement (Pension Plan)., 1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/1/68.
      - Item 15: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Item 16: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Item 17: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Agreement (Pension Plan)., 1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/1/71.
      - Item 18: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Agreement (Pension Plan)., 1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/1/71. Copy 2.
      - Item 19: Clark Equipment Company, Apprentice Standards, 1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        7/1/71.
      - Item 20: Clark Equipment Company, Apprentice Standards, 1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        7/1/71. Copy 2.
      - Item 21: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/1/74 - 5/2/77.
      - Item 22: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/1/74 - 5/2/77. Copy 2.
      - Item 23: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Agreement (Pension Plan)., 1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/1/74.
      - Item 24: Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Agreement (Pension Plan)., 1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 32)
        5/1/74. Copy 2.
    - Clark Equipment Company, Supplemental Agreement (Pension Plan)., 1977-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Item 4: Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan and AIW, Local 623, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Item 5: Clark Equipment Company, Pension Plan and Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 33)
        5/1/80.
      - Item 6: Clark Equipment Company, Pension Plan and Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, 1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 1, Folder 33)
        5/1/80. Copy 2.
    - Clark Equipment Company and IAM, Local 701 (Automobile Mechanics), 1956-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      12/4/56 - 12/4/59
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company and IAM, Local 701 (Automobile Mechanics), 1956-1959; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 1)
        12/4/56 - 12/4/59.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company and IAM, Local 701 (Automobile Mechanics)., 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 2, Folder 1)